saralvaastu.com 2010-12-10

# Saral Vaastu

Saralvaastu.com is committed towards maintaining the privacy of information related to its associates and users. We do not disclose information about your visits to our portal or personal information that you may give us, to any outside sources. 

We do not disclose any personal information to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes that could be used to personally identify you, such as your password, credit card number and bank account number. Saralvaastu.com marketing partners or advertisers have got their separate privacy and data collection policies that may be different or less protective than ours. Saralvaastu.com disclaims any responsibility or liability for our marketing partners' independent information handling policies and we recommend you are careful and responsible when providing personal information while interacting with any third party while online. 

Saralvaastu.com collects personal information of the user visiting the site using the method of signing up with the web site. This personal information may comprise of your name, email address, date of birth, gender, gender, contact address, pin code or any other information deemed necessary by Saralvaastu.com from time to time to be collected.

Saralvaastu.com uses the information for the purpose of making the content more customizable and for contacting the users for special offers and new products and services. Saralvaastu.com will not rent or sell the personally identifiable information to the third party. 

Saralvaastu.com may disclose your personal information about you to third parties when: 

  1. We get your consent to share the information;
  2. It is necessary to share your information for getting the product or service requested by you delivered;
  3. It is required to cooperate with the investigations of some intentional unlawful activities; 
  4. Disclosing your information is necessary to protect and defend the rights and related property of Saralvaastu.com. And that of its visitors;
  5. In case the ownership or assets of Saralvaastu.com is getting transferred to third party or in the case of bankruptcy of Saralvaastu.com.

Saralvaastu.com may amend this policy from time to time. Please refer to this page from time to time to see these new features. Saralvaastu.com may provide the aggregated personal demographic data of members to advertisers to make them understand the targeted audience. 

Site and Service Updates: We may send updates to members regarding the website and service announcement updates using the digital delivery mode.

 **Collection of Information and Its Use:** For understanding the pattern of traffic and to serve the traffic in more effective and efficient manner by supplying the more effective content, we along with our third party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. For better traffic analysis purpose and for giving the authentic details to our advertisers, we use cookies and web beacons for compiling statistical data. The other relevant information includes IP addresses, browser types, operating systems, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. 

**Provision of Products and Services:** Saralvaastu.com reserves the right to limit the provision of any product or service to any person, geographic area or jurisdiction it so desires, in its sole discretion and to limit the quantities of any such product or service that it provides. Any offer for any product or service made on Saralvaastu.com is void where prohibited.

 **Linked Sites:** Saralvaastu.com is not responsible in any way towards the genuineness and accuracy and updation of the content of the linked sites, which have been linked, to Saralvaastu.com. These links have been provided to you for your convenience and the placement of link at Saralvaastu.com doesn’t imply any endorsement by us about the link and the linked site. If you choose to purchase the product or service from any of the linked site or from any of the merchants and advertisers which appear on Saralvaastu.com, you release us from any or all claims you may have regarding the third party’s failure to deliver or perform. The user accesses the links available at Saralvaastu.com and related sites at his own risk and discretion.

 **Security:** Saralvaastu.com has security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under our control. Only authorized users have access to the information you provide. No transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secured. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of Saralvaastu.com to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your personal details, Saralvaastu.com cannot ensure that all your communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this privacy policy. You acknowledge and assume this risk when communicating with Saralvaastu.com.

 **Termination:** Saralvaastu.com reserves the right to discontinue in whole or in part any portion of Saralvaastu.com services or programs with or without notice. 

**Right to Change:** Saralvaastu.com reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time in whole or in part with or without notice. All changes will be posted to this page, and we may or may not make necessary efforts to notify you of any significant changes to this privacy policy. It becomes your responsibility to check this page to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. In case of any concern about your privacy, please write to us, we will respond to you immediately.
